That
such a top 5 math car can come out
that if something has happened then
set an alarm and come to the side
hello hello friends
I am asking you to comment so that a
video of the interface industry was made that a
car has met with an accident and we
can see it here today in this I will
tell you right now what is the first
update to the country you see
my contact is Challenger Frill on the lever clip
and this predictor and this candy
crush on the roof as per the loot both are bad
Haryana advisor lives who has looted
Haryana chilli and two
calls will have to be checked its share is also bad
when you will have to check some tips here
in November year you may have to do some tips now it may be
broken but the rest
looks good because you will have to check
and after that you should put a little bit of Piola
rate point inside this full number
if you do something it will have to be changed a little the
rewarded share and on the bottom side it is
written 125 which is iron ore and when
it has to be sent
and its
difference can be there the alignment of the front belt will also have to be
checked and small amount of
tips toe  I am wondering whether this opening will
go next to it or will it be fixed or not, right now it does
not seem that it will be straight,
Hindi, we are looking at how much it has rotated
on the handle, see how much it has rotated,
friend, now see its song, this one your tender
and this one express schedule will have to be changed, that
we will also have your bank and
Hindi retention and if asked
on the proposal, this silencer will have to be
a special police in the vehicles and on top of that,
this
rear panel of this website on which trust has to be
developed, that is not because let's
start dismantling, start chat
as you can see, let's start in this,
as this process will proceed, I will
tell you about dismantling your wart run game,
which is getting changed in the last week, so
which pass costs how much and how much is the total,
which five changes are there, first of all, the
vehicle is completely made in India,
then this video will be made, then I
can give you all a surprise in Mexico, now the
silencer has been instructed, how much
damage will it cause, if the silencer is passed, whereas for
Rs.17500
Rs.17500  The silencer has passed or the
first one has been successful, so if you want to see information related to vehicle
speed repairing, especially TVS, then
subscribe to our channel.
If you are new, we
still have to
complete 1070, for which the camera
is 870 and we need 130 fiber, the target will be
achieved. If we achieve the target,
we will be
able to make very good videos and give you relief. Therefore,
you are requested to subscribe.
If you have come, then everyone who is watching our old
traditions and thank you very much.
Watch the entire video. It will give you some information about how much has been
changed in the vehicle
and which parts were changed
and in the end we will tell you how much the total of the vehicle is and
how many claims have been passed by the insurance company and
how much the customer has to pay. We will tell you in all the details in the end.
So
watch the video till the end or you can read it now, there is no
problem, if you
watch the video, come
I
[Music] I am
not coming tomorrow,
I feel like leaving it at home,
where is your phone,
send me the photo, I will keep it, apart from this  No
one knows
who the real middle-aged man is, how to
update academic 2017, stop it,
send a message
to
remove your pimples,
I
[Music] am
so bad
that I kept roaming around the office for A, it
is old
[Music] it has
happened
[Music] do it, the
picture
was the
biggest failure, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it,
when we now say what is up to 5 kg,
[Music]
we, do it, it has happened, okay,
Commerce Secretary, do it,
orchestra England,
Jai Hind
MP3,
this is
our
Ghagra Choli,
[Music]
that Ajay,
Ajay, I should come,
nothing happens, he
drinks alcohol, what has
happened,
Adnan Sami saw the person,
phone
number, it has
happened, it has happened, it has happened, do it,
as you can see, complete
dismantling has been done and the stuff has been kept
selected  So 5 photos of all the items have to be
sent to the insurance company so that it can be seen how much
damage is there, which is there, which is there and what is
not there and according to that which
parts will be repaired or not, accordingly
you have to change it,
send it to all in the P tag, entertaining, if the fifth one is
not passed by the insurance company then it will be charged, after passing the
customs they will pass it to them, its
minimum will be like this, which insurance it is, it
depends on which one is passed,
how much will it cost,
if you want to go or not, brother, will the can
sense number be correct, then we will
make a detailed video for that, if you ask by commenting, then
as we can see, now
this light is being checked in full detail,
which one is broken, where is it stuck,
as you can see, but if it is slightly
broken then this also has to be pressed and this
silencer has to be done, it has to be done in a special edition,
this reappearance jokes teacher has to be sent
or font wala khabar
nirit khabar, say completely
from the spread, this is your
front panel completely  You have to
change the spread of 600 so that they can change their DP on the site,
not
this conference of sexy film bf is completely located
that
[music]
is the bank of Naxalism
[music] there is a
lever
delete on WhatsApp
[music]
or there was a display of this, the best
way to alert this is to keep it in the tiles which is in
complaint against and press it,
here it will work, is it a bank or not or cough
and on has been completely banned, see
its Puri and Singh have it, then
this phone is the final phone fat burning or on the
silencer,
friends, it seems that when you
sent these photos, you did not think whose silencer would
pass, you will get the full result of 100, but on A, the
entire spread campaign is starting, you can
see the shape of the building and it
seems to be doing this, now they have made it
two by firing indiscriminately, as
you can see,
a bear bottom panel and both side panels are being
installed
and the front side panel and the
carrier Gautam panel are being tightened, net
school is being installed
and completely ready
A
[Music]
Send a message
solution is being done jointly
18 MLAs are simply being installed
[Music]
and are being locked or the front is being
tolled it has happened
that the font of the powers when start a little
jhala does
not take even a moment it is
not the smell plate that is old we will have to
see the bill then we will know
I just have such a
beautiful
failure
that the department was making the gate that
while installing it they are giving
that a
[Music]
that
this is being done in the handle that the
handlebars are being increased
this front Anand satellite has been installed tolled
whatsapp in
it small plastic lips are being put
which does not break the problem of calling from the net it has to be done
MP3 it has to be done
torch light and mite the want panel is being completely
routed from
all sides it has been done
by Chanakya
[Music]
that this is being installed on the battery
yes it is done the
phone side is now completely ready  It is looking
every year side, you
can see that the silencer is not fitted, friends there are so many
secrets of Rs.17500 that it was fitted but it was a
new car, it was a company car, the
silencer should also be approved, if it was
not an old car then the silencer would not have been approved, ah
how are you, do it
and tell me,
set the alarm, start, it is
coming,
ah
[Music] the
real story
[Music] do it, do it,
you just do it, ah
fuel tank, Akbar,
how to get rid of it,
check it, the clock is working, then this
reappearance has happened
[Music] tell
Ajay
that ah
and Jethalal have happened, so that we will be
first,
ah has happened, ah, do it,
so I welcome you once again to the channel,
now it is time to discuss the final
bill of a car and how much has the society spent, how much has the
insurance company spent,
before that news, now see,
after the profile rally of the car, the gas
officer had married earlier and now you will
see that it is not brown or
shining,
so what all things are there  Member, let me
tell you again, I have the bill of this vehicle in my hand, I will
start telling from the top,
silencer can be used, it
gives a clean look,
2014 for ₹100 and cut era below ₹12 for ₹100,
carrier panel black 756 for use,
10 million rupees have been spent for the body, 349 rupees and the
racer has also changed, the middle cover of 421 powers has been
changed, now the
wire was changed for ₹1, black color and light visor
300 for ₹40, the front panel which is red,
change it, 1440 rupees, side panelists and the one which was
showing 25, get it done, joint 1365 will
stop the suicide, that is, there is a
way to hold the west handle like Shiv and Villain Hunter, 1484 has
so much respect, payment time was charged,
apart from that there was labor charge which is for length
alignment and for opening and fitting of the vehicle,
whoever did the work, everything together is in the
arena  There were a total of 20
petitioners, 272 of them used, out of this the insurance
company which is ICC has covered
thousands of rupees and the customer had to pay around ₹500, the
fruit of this much waiting is ₹5000, that's all you
get in today's video,
in the next video, if you have not subscribed to the channel then
subscribe and if you
want to know any opinion about the video then please
tell us by commenting in the comment box and if you
want to ask any question in this car service network then
ask in the comment or thank you bro,
he is taking pride in watching,
let's do it now